horchow.com 2019-01-08

# Privacy Policy & Terms Of Use at Horchow

This website ("website") is operated by The Neiman Marcus Group, LLC, which includes Neiman Marcus stores, Neiman Marcus Direct, Horchow, and Bergdorf Goodman ("Neiman Marcus" or "we" or "us"). This privacy policy only covers information collected at this website, and does not cover any information collected offline by Neiman Marcus (unless specifically stated). All Neiman Marcus websites, including NeimanMarcus.com, BergdorfGoodman.com, Horchow.com, and LastCall.com, are currently covered by this privacy policy. The purpose of this policy is to fully inform you of how we handle your personal data.

We are committed to handling your personal information with high standards of information security. We take appropriate physical, electronic, and administrative steps to maintain the security and accuracy of personally identifiable information we collect, including limiting the number of people who have physical access to our database servers, as well as employing electronic security systems and password protections that guard against unauthorized access. Our website uses encryption technology, such as Transport Layer Security (TLS) to protect your personal information during data transport. TLS encrypts ordering information such as your name, address, and credit card number. Our Customer Care center and stores also operate over a private, secure network. Please note that email is not encrypted and is not considered to be a secure means of transmitting any sensitive information, including your credit card information.

Personal information provided on the website and online credit card transactions are transmitted through a secure server using TLS encryption technology. When the letters "http" in the URL change to "https," the "s" indicates you are in a secure area employing TLS; also, your browser may give you a pop-up message that you're about to enter a secure area.

You may purchase online merchandise by calling toll-free 1.888.888.4757, 24 hours a day, seven days a week. One of our customer service associates will gladly take your order. 

To help us achieve our goal of providing the highest quality products and services, we use information from our interactions with you and other customers, as well as from other parties. Because we respect your privacy, we have implemented procedures to ensure that your personal information is handled in a safe, secure, and responsible manner.

As we continue to develop our website and take advantage of advances in technology to improve the services we offer, this privacy policy likely will change. We therefore encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. 

This Privacy Policy was last updated on May 25, 2018. 

We may ask you to provide personally identifiable information at various times and places on this website. In some cases, if you choose not to provide us with the requested information, you may not be able to access the entire website or participate in all of its features. 

* Visit our website
* Enter information on our website
* Shop with Neiman Marcus online, through our catalogs, or in our stores
* Provide information in other ways such as by subscribing to our emails or consenting to mobile messaging 

We may collect the following personally identifiable information: 

  * Your name
  * Address
  * Telephone number
  * Birth date 
  * Email address 
  * Your account number if you pay by credit or debit card or by check 
  * We may also collect your driver's license number in connection with certain gift card purchases, or when you apply for our private label credit card
  * If you use one of our services, or participate in one of our surveys, promotions, or sweepstakes, we may ask for additional information, such as your interests, or product preferences
  * From your purchases and other interactions with us, we obtain information concerning the specific products or services you purchase or use

When you register with us as an online customer, we may ask for additional information, such as your favorite designers. During registration of your customer account, we collect and implement your personal data in order to finalize the order process, as well as customize your personal shopping experience. Your data will be transmitted to third parties for certain purposes, for example, to complete your current order or to third parties who assist Neiman Marcus with its marketing efforts, subject to applicable data privacy laws. 

For customers based in the United States, when you visit this website, whether or not you are logged in or enter any personal information, our web server automatically collects anonymous information such as log data and IP addresses, and may collect general information concerning your location. For European Union customers, such information is collected once your consent is provided. We may use this collected information for a number of purposes, such as improving our site design, product assortments, customer service, and special promotions.

When you visit one of our stores or shop via the NM mobile app, we may also automatically collect information about your geo-location based, in part, upon which wireless network has been accessed. When this happens we attempt to de-identify the information, which means that we remove or change (e.g., hash) certain pieces of information that might be used to link the data to you, or to your device. We will not attempt to re-identify geo-location information (i.e., link it to you or your device) unless you affirmatively give us permission to collect geo-location information about you. If you give us such permission, you can later decide to opt-out. To disable geo-location on your mobile device, open your Settings app, and tap Privacy. Then, tap on Location Services. Scroll down until you see the "NM" app and tap on the toggle on the right hand side so that the toggle is no longer green.

Our mobile applications will not transmit geo-location information about you to us unless you give them permission to do so.

Some web browsers and devices permit you to broadcast a preference that you not be "tracked" online. At this time we do not modify your experience based upon whether such a signal is broadcast.

The Information We Collect was last updated May 25, 2018. 

### How We Use the Information We Collect

Neiman Marcus may collect your personal data, subject to applicable data privacy laws. The data we collect is necessary for the operation of our business and in our legitimate interest. We may collect information to:

  * Complete your purchase transactions
  * Provide the services you request 
  * Send you our catalogues and other marketing offerings
  * Identify your product and service preferences, so we can notify you of new or additional products, services, and promotions that might be of interest to you
  * Notify you of product recalls or provide other information concerning products you have purchased 
  * Improve our merchandise selections, customer service, and overall shopping experience 

Neiman Marcus does not subject you to decisions which might have a legal effect on you due solely to the automated processing of personal data.

For US residents, we undertake marketing only in compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act, the Telephone Consumer Protection Act, and other applicable laws. For EU residents, we undertake marketing only with your expressive affirmative consent and in compliance with applicable data privacy laws. EU residents will not be added to the marketing lists unless they have already provided such express affirmative consent.

### Others With Whom We Share Your Information

All of the information that we collect, as described above, may be shared among all Neiman Marcus entities, including Horchow, Bergdorf Goodman, and Last Call.

Service Providers: We also may disclose information to outside companies that help us bring you the products and services we offer. For example, we may work with an outside company to: (a) manage a database of customer information; (b) assist us in distributing emails; (c) assist us with marketing and data collection; (d) provide us storage and analysis; (d) provide fraud prevention; and (e) provide other services designed to assist us in maximizing our business potential. We require that these outside companies agree to keep confidential all information we share with them, use the information only to perform their obligations in our agreements with them, and abide by applicable data privacy laws. 

Other Companies: Neiman Marcus may partner with select vendors to market goods and services to you which, based on your preferences, we believe may be of interest. If you do not wish for your information to be shared with these carefully selected outside companies, you may write to Neiman Marcus Customer Care at P.O. Box 650589, Dallas, TX, 75265-0589 or call toll-free 1-888-888-4757.

Business Transitions: We may transfer or share a copy of your personal information in the event that Neiman Marcus or one of its properties, affiliates, or subsidiaries goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition, or selling a portion of its assets. You will be notified via email or prominent notice on our website prior to a change of ownership or control of your personal information, if your personal information will be used contrary to this policy. However, nothing in this Privacy Policy is intended to interfere with the ability of Neiman Marcus to transfer all or part of its business and/or assets to an affiliate or independent third party at any time, for any purpose, without any limitation whatsoever. Neiman Marcus specifically reserves the right to transfer or share a copy of personally identifiable information collected from its websites to the buyer of that portion of its business relating to that information.

Compliance with Law: We may provide access to information when legally required to do so, to cooperate with police investigations or other legal proceedings, to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our website, to limit our legal liability, and to protect our rights or to protect the rights, property, or safety of visitors of this website or the public. 

Neiman Marcus partners with advertising companies to place our advertising on publisher websites on the Internet. These advertising companies collect anonymous information about your visits to our web site. This technology involves the use of third party cookies which allow them to develop personalized advertising so that it directly relates to offers that may be of interest to you. To choose to opt-out of this service we have with our third-party advertising partner, [click here](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/). 

### Your Choices Regarding Use of the Information We Collect

We provide you with a number of choices regarding our handling of your nonpublic personally identifiable information.

Emails: If you do not want to receive email from Neiman Marcus or its affiliates you can click on the "Manage Your Email Preferences" link at the bottom of any email communication sent by us. Choose "Unsubscribe" at the bottom of the page that opens. 

Direct Mail or Telephone Marketing: If you provided your email address to a sales associate and no long wish to receive in-store or omni-channel promotions, you can unsubscribe by clicking the "Unsubscribe" link at the bottom of the e-receipt, or the link provided at the bottom of an email send by the sales associate. You may also email [storeemailoptout@NeimanMarcus.com](mailto:storeemailoptout@NeimanMarcus.com). 

You also have the option to write to Neiman Marcus Customer Care at: P.O. Box 650589, Dallas, TX 75265-0589.

If you choose to write to us, please include your name and address, and state one of the following:

"NO MAIL OFFERS" (if you don't want to receive offers by mail);  
"NO PHONE OFFERS" (if you don't want to receive offers by phone); or  
"NO PHONE OR MAIL OFFERS" (if you don't want to receive either). 

These requests may also be made by calling our toll-free number: 1-888-888-4757.

Because customer lists often are prepared well in advance of an offering (sometimes a few months before the offer is made), you may continue to receive some offers after you send us a request not to use your information for specified marketing purposes. We appreciate your patience and understanding in giving us time to carry out your request.

Mobile Messaging: If you've signed up for mobile messaging (e.g., SMS and MMS) offers but later decide you no longer wish to receive them, simply follow the opt-out instructions included in the mobile message.

Your California Privacy Rights

Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal customer information we share with third parties or corporate affiliates for those third parties or corporate affiliates' direct marketing purposes. That notice will identify the categories of information shared and will include a list of the third parties and affiliates with which it was shared, along with their names and addresses. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: Neiman Marcus Customer Care, P.O. Box 650589, Dallas, TX 75265-0589. Please allow 30 days for a response. 

### Cookies, Web Beacons, and How We Use Them

A "cookie" is a small data file stored by your Web browser on your computer or mobile device [hard drive]. It allows us to recognize your computer (but not specifically who is using it) upon entering our site by associating the identification numbers in the cookie with other customer information you have provided us. That customer information is stored on our secured database. A "web beacon" or "pixel tag" or "clear gif" is typically a one-pixel image, used to pass information from your computer or mobile device to a website.

We use cookies and web beacons to keep track of what you have in your shopping cart and to remember you when you return to the website as well as to identify the pages you click on during your visit to our site and the name of the website you visited immediately before clicking to NeimanMarcus.com. We use this information to improve our site design, product assortments, customer service, and special promotions. You can, of course, disable cookies and web beacons on your computer by indicating this in the preferences or options menus in your browser. All users may view our offers without having enabled the cookies. If you opt not to accept cookies, however, you may not be able to benefit from the full features of our site. We may also use web beacons, and other technologies, to help track whether our communications are reaching you, to measure their effectiveness, or to collect certain non-personal information about your computer, device, or browser in order to allow us to better design future communications to you. 

Some of the cookies we use are automatically deleted from your hard drive after the end of the browser session (session cookies). We also use cookies that remain on your hard drive for a certain period of time (between one day and five years, depending on the cookie) after the browser session. When you revisit our site, it will automatically recall the country and language you selected at your last visit to our website. These "persistent cookies" are stored on your hard drive and will be deleted by the browser after the given time. You also have the option to delete these cookies at any time through your browser.

We may contract with third parties who may use cookies and web beacons and collect information on our behalf or provide services such as credit card processing, shipping, promotional services, or data management. We call them our Customer Care Partners. These third parties are prohibited by our contract with them from sharing that information with anyone other than us or our other Customer Care Partners.

We use third party retargeting and remarketing features on our website. These technologies allow us to address internet users who previously visited the site by personalized advertising on our partners' websites. For this purpose, the retargeting or remarketing provider will store a cookie on your hard drive. Based on the cookie technology, anonymous user details will be stored - for example, the advertising you received from us or clicked, the products you viewed, or whether you made a purchase. 

You may stop the use of the retargeting and/or remarketing feature by accessing the third party providers' cookie opt-out pages via the following links:

Google: <https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en>  
Criteo : <https://www.criteo.com/privacy/>  
NAI Opt Out Tool: <http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/>  
Digital Advertising Alliance Opt Out Tool: <http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2#!/>

NMG websites use third party web analytics to monitor site and app traffic and visitor behaviors.

Google Analytics: To learn more about Google Analytics' privacy practices and any opt-out choices it offers, [click here](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245). (https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245)

Adobe Analytics: To learn more about Adobe Analytics??? privacy practices or to opt-out of cookies set to facilitate reporting by Adobe Analytics, [click here](https://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html). (https://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html)

Please note that your opt-out status may be maintained by placement of an "opt-out" cookie on your device. If the cookie is removed or deleted, or you upgrade to a new version of your browser, change browsers or visit us from a different device, you will need to repeat this process to indicate your preference.

This Cookies, Web Beacons, and How We Use Them was last updated on May 25, 2018.

Use of Social Plugins

We use social plugins of several providers on our website in the respective standard plugin:

  * The Facebook ("Share") button of Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA. The button is marked with the Facebook logo and the addition ("Share").
  * The social plugin of Twitter, operated by Twitter, Inc., 795 Folsom St., Suite 600, San Francisco, CA 94107, USA. This button is marked with the Twitter logo.
  * The social plugin of Weibo, operated by Weibo Corporation, No. 8 Sina Plaza, Courtyard 10, the West, XiBeiWang E. Road, HaiDian District, Beijing 100080, China. This button is marked by the Weibo logo.

When you access one of our websites containing any of the above plugins, the plugin provider may store a cookie in your browser. We have no control over the scope of the data collected by the provider by means of the plugin.

The plugins may provide their hosts with information such as the date and time of your visit to our website(s), your IP address, or the type of browser you use. If you are logged on to your account with the plugin provider while visiting our websites, the provider may match this information and any data you enter to your user account, should you interact with the plugins. - for instance if you click the corresponding button on our website or post a comment. Your recommendations or comments may be displayed as information, together with your profile name and photograph, in the relevant provider's service - for instance in search results or in your user profile, or at other places on websites and in advertisements on the internet.

Even if you are not a member of the relevant provider's service, the provider may under certain circumstances nevertheless obtain and store your IP address. For the purpose and scope of data collection and further processing and use of your data by the provider, as well as your related rights and opt-out possibilities to protect your privacy, please see the privacy policies of Facebook, Twitter, and Weibo. 

If you are a member of the relevant service and do not wish the service provider to collect data on you via our websites and connect them with the member data stored by the provider, you should log off your provider account before visiting our internet sites.

This Cookies, Web Beacons, and How We Use Them was last updated on May 25, 2018. 

### Children's Privacy

Protecting children's privacy is important to us. Our website is a general audience site. We do not collect or maintain information from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is targeted to attract anyone under 13. We also do not send email correspondence to anyone who tells us that they are under the age of 13 without their parent's consent.

Children under the age of 13 should always ask their parents or guardians for permission before providing any personal information to anyone online. We urge parents and guardians to participate in their children's online activities and use parental control or other web filtering technology to supervise children's access to the web. 

### Links to Other Sites

While visiting our websites, you may link to websites operated by our business partners or other third parties. This does not mean that we endorse these websites. We do not make any representations or warranties about any website you may access through this website. They are independent from us, and we have no control over, or responsibility for, their information or activities.

In addition, our privacy practices may differ from those of these other sites. If you provide personal information at one of those sites, you are subject to the privacy policy of the operator of that site, not the Neiman Marcus Privacy Policy. Make sure you understand any website's privacy policies before providing personal information.

### Online Account Registration

To make online shopping faster and easier, you may register with NeimanMarcus.com. As a registered customer, you only have to enter your shipping addresses and billing information once; that information will be securely stored with us for your future use. Using your name and a password of your choice, you may access your account online at any time to add, delete, or change information.

If you are using a public computer, we strongly encourage you to LOG OUT at the conclusion of your session. Your information will still be stored with us but it will not be accessible to anyone else from that computer.

### Express Checkout

Express Checkout allows users to purchase a single item of merchandise through an expedited checkout process. By enabling Express Checkout, you agree that your payment method may be charged and your purchase completed by way of the Express Checkout process. Express Checkout is available only for purchase originating from and shipping to the Continental United States. 

Express Checkout Last Updated February 25, 2016

### Data Storage, Access, The Right to be Forgotten, and Dispute Resolution

We store personal data for different periods of time consistent with the purposes for which they were originally collected, as subsequently further authorized, or when required or allowed under applicable law. 

EU residents have certain data subject rights which may be subject to limitations and/or restrictions. These rights may include the right to: (i) request access to and rectification or erasure of their personal data; (ii) obtain restriction of processing or to object to processing of their personal data; and (iii) the right to data portability. If you wish to exercise one of the above mentioned rights, please send us your request via email to: privacy@NeimanMarcus.com. Individuals in Europe may also have the right to lodge a complaint about the processing of their personal data with their local data protection authority. 

Once we receive your email, Neiman Marcus can provide you with that data or at least an explanation of why we cannot do so in the particular context, such as if responding to the request would be unreasonably expensive. If your concerns cannot be resolved, we can enter into appropriate third-party neutral dispute resolution. 

### Data Controller, Data Protection Officer

Neiman Marcus, One Marcus Square, 1618 Main Street, Dallas, Texas 75201 is responsible for your privacy protection and is the official service provider. If you have questions regarding our website, the following information, or if you would like to contact our privacy protection representative, please contact us at [privacy@NeimanMarcus.com](mailto:privacy@NeimanMarcus.com)

### Acceptance

By using this website, you accept the policies set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

### Any questions?

We'll be happy to provide additional information or answer any questions. Please call us at toll-free 1.888.888.4757, or write to our Customer Care department at P.O. Box 650589, Dallas, TX 75265-0589.

Last updated on May 25, 2018.
